swoopo.ca 2009-11-26

# Auction | Cheap TV laptop ipod auctions - bid & win on Swoopo

**PRIVACY POLICY**

**Scope**  
Swoopo.ca (“Swoopo”) is a service provided by Entertainment Shopping Inc. ( **“Entertainment Shopping,“ “.we,” “our,** ” or **“.us,”** as may be, herein). We recognize and respect your personal privacy. This policy (this “Privacy Policy”) describes all aspects of gathering information while you are visiting Swoopo, how we handle your personal information for our services, and all further permissible uses of such information.  

This Privacy Policy is incorporated by reference into the Terms & Conditions of Swoopo. (See here for the current Terms & Conditions). This Privacy Policy conforms to the _provisions of the Personal Information Protection and Electronic Documents Act_ (Canada) ( **“PIPEDA”** ).

By accepting the Privacy Policy and the Terms and Conditions in registration, you expressly consent to our collection, storage, use and disclosure of your personal information as described in this Privacy Policy. This Privacy Policy is effective upon acceptance for new and existing users and is otherwise effective immediately upon being posted on Swoopo. 

**Data Collection**  
You may visit Swoopo at any time without providing your identity or revealing any personal information about yourself. However, when you visit our website, we may collect and store your computer and connection information, statistics on page views, traffic to and from Swoopo, ad data, IP address and standard web log information and information from other companies, such as demographic and navigation data.  
For you to actively participate in Swoopo, however, we do need some of your personal information. Once you provide us with your required personal information, you are no longer anonymous. In providing us with your personal information, you consent to the transfer and storage of such information on our servers.  
In connection with your registration and use of Swoopo We may collect and store the following personal information:  

  * email address and physical contact information including but not limited to your name, address, date of birth and telephone number;
  * all transactional information based on your activities on Swoopo;
  * shipping, billing and other information relating to any purchase or shipping;
  * any correspondence sent to us;
  * financial information, such as your credit card information; and
  * other supplemental information from third parties.

**Use of Data**   
Our primary purpose in collecting personal information is to provide you with a safe, smooth, efficient, and customized experience. You agree that we may use your personal information to:

  * provide the services and customer support you request;
  * resolve disputes, collect fees, and troubleshoot problems;
  * prevent potentially prohibited or illegal activities, and enforce our Terms and Conditions and the provisions of this Privacy Policy;
  * customize, measure and improve our services, content and advertising;
  * inform you about our services, targeted marketing, service updates, and promotional offers; and
  * compare information for accuracy and verify it with third parties.

We routinely update personal information because such updating is critical to fulfill the purposes for which the information was collected in the first place, as outlined above in this Privacy Policy. You expressly consent to our routinely updating your personal information and, where appropriate, soliciting such updates from you.

**Disclosure of Personal Data**  
We may disclose personal information to respond to legal requirements, enforce our policies, respond to claims that a listing or other content violates the rights of others, or protect anyone’s rights, property, or safety. Such information will be disclosed in accordance with applicable laws and regulations in Canada or outside of Canada.

We may also share your personal information with third parties assisting our business operations under contract or seeking our co-operation, including but not limited to: fraud investigators and debt collection agencies and personnel; law enforcement or other governmental officials if and as required by law; and, other business entities, should we plan to merge with or be acquired by those business entities.

Without limiting the above, in an effort to respect your privacy and our ability to keep the community free from bad actors, we will not otherwise disclose your personal information to law enforcement, other government officials, or other third parties without a subpoena, court order or substantially similar legal procedure, except when we believe in good faith that the disclosure of information is necessary to prevent imminent physical harm or financial loss or to report suspected illegal activity.

**Providing Data within the Corporate Group**  
We are a member of the Entertainment Shopping Corporate Group. You are consenting to allowing your data to be provided to and among different members of this corporate group. We assure you that should data be provided this way, security and confidentiality will be guaranteed with no change, and that the data will continue to be subject to this Privacy Policy.

**Your Information on Swoopo**  
Once you have been approved as a registered user with Swoopo, you will be required to choose a user name. This user name will be displayed throughout Swoopo and therefore provided to the public. Unless you associate your user name with your personal information, other users will not be able to personally identify your activities on Swoopo.

When visiting Swoopo from a public or shared computer, certain information about you, such as your user name, may also be visible to others who may use such computer after your use.

**Access, Review and Change of Personal Data**  
You can access, review and change most of your personal information by logging on to Swoopo at any time. However, some of your personal information can only be changed by contacting our Customer Service. You are required to promptly update your personal information if changes occur or if any information is inaccurate.

**Revoking Consent/Deleting Your Account**  
You may withdraw your consent to the collection, use, and disclosure of personal information at any time. Upon such a request, or upon a request to terminate, delete, or de-activate your Swoopo account, we will close your account and remove your personal information from public view as soon as reasonably possible, based upon your account activity and in accordance with applicable law, including PIPEDA. We do retain certain personal information from closed accounts in order to comply with law, prevent fraud, collect any fees owed, resolve disputes, troubleshoot problems, assist with any investigations, enforce our Terms and Conditions, and take other actions otherwise required and/or permitted by law.

**The Use of Cookies at our Website**  
Swoopo uses so-called “cookies” which are files that are stored on your computer that can be retrieved to assist in customizing your experience with the online service. The information saved supports the functionality of the site, for example, by keeping track of your visual preferences or controlling the frequency of .pop-up. windows. You are free to prevent cookies from being saved on your hard drive by adjusting the corresponding settings in your browser. However, we would like to point out that turning off these settings may result in limited functionality.

**Security Measures**  
Your Swoopo account and profile and the information contained therein are password protected. Please note that you are not permitted to provide your password to anyone else. Swoopo will never ask for your password in e-mails that you receive unexpectedly or that you did not request. Please remember to log out of your account and to close your internet browser window when you leave Swoopo; this is especially important if you use a PC in public locations. (You may also wish to delete your browsing history after each visit to Swoopo; again, this is critical if you use a PC in public locations.) At present, this is the safest way to ensure that no one has access to your personal information. We assume no liability for the abuse of login data and passwords used.

We treat data as an asset that must be protected. We use lots of security measures to protect your personal information against unauthorized access and disclosure. However, although we work very hard to protect your privacy, we cannot promise, and you must not and cannot expect, that your personal information or private communications will always remain private.

**Protection from Web Crawlers or Spam**  
Swoopo assures you that we will use your e-mail address with your express consent only for the purposes stated in the Terms & Conditions. We will not rent or sell your e-mail address to third parties, and we will endeavour to prevent your e-mail address from being recorded by “web crawlers” or “web spiders” to the best of our ability. If you believe that your e-mail address has been recorded in this way, please let us know immediately.

**General**  
We may amend this Privacy Policy at any time by posting the amended terms on Swoopo. All amended terms automatically take effect immediately after they are initially posted on Swoopo.
